[
    {
        "question": "What is the 8-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character h in the string hggmmhmaaagggaaaamaamhagamgmga?",
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 6-th apperance of the character x in the string qqyxqwvxxxxvqywyyyqvvvvvwvxyyw?",
        "answer": "y"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character d in the string bloqodoloqobodbldqllqlobloollb?",
        "answer": "l"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 4-th character after the 13-th apperance of the character x in the string nxxxxnnnxxnnxxqxqqxnxxnqxqqnnq?",
        "answer": "n"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 10-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character y in the string yrryruyuyyruryuuyrrrrrrurryyru?",
        "answer": "r"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 1-th character after the 11-th apperance of the character t in the string ytyysyttsystttyttyttyysststtyy?",
        "answer": "s"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 17-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character g in the string ggfjffgffgofojjfjjjjjfgogfjoff?",
        "answer": "j"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 4-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character u in the string bmbuhmubuhmhmuhuhbumubhumuhhmm?",
        "answer": "m"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character s in the string zssswnnssswwnzswwszwwzzhwhwnhn?",
        "answer": "s"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 8-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character a in the string hlauahhhllaalahhhhaaluauuhlalu?",
        "answer": "u"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 4-th character after the 6-th apperance of the character a in the string cecepcaeceeeaeaeaccaepacpceccc?",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 6-th character after the 12-th apperance of the character s in the string ysysssysssssysysysysysyysysyuy?",
        "answer": "y"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 21-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character s in the string dbskkfdskkkkbsbsfskbsddbskfffd?",
        "answer": "f"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 29-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character g in the string gggaqbgccagaqqbgagbcqccacgbqaq?",
        "answer": "q"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 12-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character y in the string lnmynlylllmnllnmylynyyllmlyyml?",
        "answer": "y"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 7-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character r in the string reubreeeuebbebbebbbrrreebruebu?",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character m in the string mmmmmmmooooyommyooomyyyoymooyy?",
        "answer": "o"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 7-th apperance of the character s in the string sihrhiissssshssissirrrrrrhrshh?",
        "answer": "i"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 11-th apperance of the character e in the string rdejeededeeddjejedejrrredrrerj?",
        "answer": "j"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 7-th character after the 8-th apperance of the character b in the string sbbblbllslsbbllllbblsbbllllbls?",
        "answer": "l"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character z in the string snsnsnnnssnszsnwnwznwwzzszwnss?",
        "answer": "n"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 7-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character n in the string niyibiiinbybiyniynniynyinniyby?",
        "answer": "n"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 1-th character after the 7-th apperance of the character m in the string pppypmmmpbphphmhymymppbymyhbhp?",
        "answer": "y"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 8-th character after the 6-th apperance of the character j in the string gjigjvjjiciggcgjcjgggggiggjgvv?",
        "answer": "g"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 7-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character s in the string lklsokosssvooolkvksoklllklkkvo?",
        "answer": "k"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 4-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character g in the string bgrhhrrhhrbbggrbhgbhhhghhbbbbh?",
        "answer": "g"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 9-th apperance of the character q in the string qssjsjspjsqqpqpspqssjqqsqqpsjp?",
        "answer": "s"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 8-th apperance of the character m in the string mmchmhchmchmmccmhhchmcchmcmchc?",
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 8-th character after the 9-th apperance of the character y in the string rssyhysryhsyhyyyryyryryysssshh?",
        "answer": "s"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 3-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character x in the string uyuwuywxxxwswssxuxuuwsyuyyswsy?",
        "answer": "w"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 7-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character x in the string fxfxggfgffxfgnffxnnnxggfgxgffg?",
        "answer": "f"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 4-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character n in the string igigggggingnignniginginngniggg?",
        "answer": "n"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 3-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character m in the string vfqvvffvqjvfjfmvqvmjqfjvmfmqvv?",
        "answer": "q"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 13-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character p in the string ppvaveeaevapappavevvaapavpevea?",
        "answer": "v"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 10-th apperance of the character t in the string twvvtttwtvvvttwtwwtttwwvvwtwww?",
        "answer": "v"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 11-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character d in the string djxdqjdjjxdxdqqxjjqjjxxxdjdqqj?",
        "answer": "x"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 22-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character l in the string aalalllaalaeaaealllleaellalaaa?",
        "answer": "l"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character i in the string occiccoobioooicbbcoccobooiioob?",
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 1-th character after the 7-th apperance of the character k in the string dddkyzdkedeykdzkeekyykyykdeedd?",
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 14-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character i in the string iattttaiaaiaitttttaaiiattttttt?",
        "answer": "t"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character e in the string eeepkykhyhepkepyeekkyekkyepekp?",
        "answer": "k"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character y in the string wrwyywmmmwymymmwxxmwmrwrmxrmmw?",
        "answer": "y"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 13-th character after the 7-th apperance of the character l in the string lalaaaaalxaalllallxxalxllxlaxa?",
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 1-th character after the 9-th apperance of the character z in the string ozqzxxzqzxxozooozxxqozxzoxzooo?",
        "answer": "o"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 6-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character w in the string wllaaaallalwalwaallwawlaaawlla?",
        "answer": "l"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 6-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character a in the string eveaeeveeeeveaaaevaeaeevvaaavv?",
        "answer": "v"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 17-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character w in the string wemewqewmwwwqwqmeggwwemqmqmwqe?",
        "answer": "w"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 9-th character after the 6-th apperance of the character l in the string zuuulzuelelzluzlzzzllzlullzezz?",
        "answer": "z"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 3-th character after the 9-th apperance of the character s in the string gyygyssgggsygggsggssyysysssggg?",
        "answer": "g"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character f in the string fbbbqbqqfbbqffbfffbqqfqqffqqbq?",
        "answer": "f"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 10-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character y in the string uwyupuywwyuwtuytpyuuptpuwptpww?",
        "answer": "u"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 11-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character p in the string jjupjpppujppppuujppjpuuuujjuju?",
        "answer": "u"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 20-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character d in the string fdyfqcdyyfcyfdffcccqqffqcdycyy?",
        "answer": "f"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 15-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character l in the string lolovolovvoovovvvllolvllovvvvv?",
        "answer": "v"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 10-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character z in the string nnnozzznnoznoznozonznnonzzoznn?",
        "answer": "z"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 12-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character n in the string rrnndrnrrddddddrnnnndnnnrnddrd?",
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 21-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character v in the string ivvvfffifkififfkiikvffkikikkkk?",
        "answer": "k"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 3-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character k in the string qkdckkwdqdqqwkwwwcdwkdcqqccdcd?",
        "answer": "q"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 12-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character a in the string lafallfallfalafalalalaalalfall?",
        "answer": "l"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character s in the string ccgcggqspcccpspsqqcgggpqsgpgpp?",
        "answer": "p"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 8-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character n in the string sjjrrssrsrdrdddrjsrsnsdrdnrjrr?",
        "answer": "r"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 14-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character u in the string rrbubusbbrbsbrusbsssbsusssbssr?",
        "answer": "s"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 7-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character r in the string nbtrftbfbtrnfbrrbnffrbtntbbbfn?",
        "answer": "r"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 4-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character s in the string sssqqgqsqgqsgsggsqggsssqsqqsqq?",
        "answer": "q"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character x in the string tdwddhhdwxhtxhxxhddttdxxtdhdtw?",
        "answer": "h"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character s in the string iisixixhiiigxxsiisiighsgsgsixi?",
        "answer": "i"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 14-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character j in the string coooojozccjcjzjdcojcojzdozdooc?",
        "answer": "o"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 7-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character y in the string zyzqyywoqyqzwzwwzwywowqyywoqoq?",
        "answer": "z"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 8-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character f in the string lllyzzzzfflfllyyyzflzzlyylylzy?",
        "answer": "y"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 6-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character p in the string fjeqeqqqjpfeqfepppeqpqjpqqqfff?",
        "answer": "j"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 7-th apperance of the character w in the string ccwccwwjcwwccjjjwwjcjjwjcwccjj?",
        "answer": "w"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 13-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character b in the string xbbxnbxxnxnbbnbbbxxnnbbnbnnnxx?",
        "answer": "n"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 6-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character d in the string dkkkdkndookndokkdnnnooknnoooko?",
        "answer": "n"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 8-th character after the 7-th apperance of the character u in the string cuuuauqqquqcqqucauqcuuqcqcaqqa?",
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 15-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character r in the string krsikkrisiiirskiiriirisriirksi?",
        "answer": "k"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 1-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character x in the string caadbbccccdxdxxbdcaxbdacdxccba?",
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 4-th character after the 6-th apperance of the character x in the string qoqoqoxqoxqqqxoqxqoxoqoooxqooq?",
        "answer": "q"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 13-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character h in the string pgyphyyggggggppphghpphpppygygp?",
        "answer": "g"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 7-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character q in the string wqkqckcqcckcwwckkwwwcqqwkqckwc?",
        "answer": "w"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 5-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character c in the string hicihiicchaciachaaiiahachssiah?",
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character y in the string jbbezbezezjyzzjzyeezzzezyjeejb?",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 14-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character g in the string iaapaagpaiaaigpaiaigippipgappa?",
        "answer": "p"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 1-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character d in the string ewmdbebedededmemmbdbmdwmbbedbb?",
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 6-th character after the 9-th apperance of the character i in the string ixzzizxzizzzxiiiixxxziizzzzxzx?",
        "answer": "z"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 14-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character c in the string jctgjtctcgjjgggcjjgjcjtggcjjtt?",
        "answer": "t"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 4-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character t in the string dddccteetcctcccdccetddcejeccej?",
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 7-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character d in the string fzmomfzomfozzooodfozdmddooooom?",
        "answer": "m"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 11-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character o in the string pwwwppowowpppwwooppwpoppwwowwp?",
        "answer": "w"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 8-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character f in the string ppxxtttfxfkkfxxtkkftpfxxtptpxx?",
        "answer": "t"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 10-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character u in the string ukrkffkffkuuffufffufuukkkrfrkf?",
        "answer": "k"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 4-th apperance of the character x in the string lototltolxoooootttxotottlxxlot?",
        "answer": "o"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 13-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character l in the string luuclcuulcllucuclcluclcullllcu?",
        "answer": "l"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 11-th apperance of the character q in the string dgggdqdqqgddqgqqdqgqqgqqggdgdd?",
        "answer": "g"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 9-th character after the 8-th apperance of the character m in the string meokmomsemmkooekomkmmokmmkomoo?",
        "answer": "o"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character v in the string vwmyywmyywmymwvwywmvwwyvwmwvwy?",
        "answer": "y"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 13-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character l in the string aaalalccdclladddcaladcdalldacc?",
        "answer": "l"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 21-th character after the 2-th apperance of the character v in the string kwkwwvkvkkwkwwwwkkkvvvkkvkkvww?",
        "answer": "w"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 18-th character after the 5-th apperance of the character f in the string vffvfggfbvkffvfbggfvfgfbvgggbg?",
        "answer": "g"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 4-th character after the 1-th apperance of the character c in the string cisgcossogicggscgsossgsiososoo?",
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 8-th character after the 3-th apperance of the character p in the string innxsnsxxppnxxsnspnsxpnsnpixnx?",
        "answer": "p"
    }
]